const questionList = [
    {
        number: 1,
        question: "How many times was Ross divorced?",
        option: [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4"],
        correct: "3"
    },
    {
        number: 2,
        question: "Where was Rachel an assistant buyer?",
        option: [
            "Macyâ€™s",
            "Saks Fifth Avenue",
            "Bloomingdale's",
            "Neiman Marcus"],
        correct: "Bloomingdale's"
    },
    {
        number: 3,
        question: "Finish the line: I mean, isn't that just ______?",
        "option": [
            "kick-you-in-the-crotch, spit-on-your-neck fantastic?",
            "kick-you-in-the-gut, spit-on-your-face fantastic?",
            "kick-you-in-the-shin, yank-out-your-hair fantastic?",
            "kick-you-in-the-knee, slap-you-on-your-face fantastic?"],
        correct: "kick-you-in-the-crotch, spit-on-your-neck fantastic?"
    },
    {
        number: 4,
        question: "Which FRIENDS are siblings?",
        "option": [
            "Monica and Ross",
            "Rachel and Monica",
            "Phoebe and Joey",
            "Chandler and Joey"],
        correct: "Monica and Ross"
    },
    {
        number: 5,
        question: "Who did Rachel almost marry?",
        "option": [
            "Paolo",
            "Barry",
            "Richard",
            "Joey"],
        correct: "Barry"
    },
    {
        number: 6,
        question: "What is Joey's catchphrase?",
        "option": [
            "Hey what's up?",
            "How's it hanging?",
            "How you doin?",
            "How are ya?"],
        correct: "How you doin?"
    },
    {
        number: 7,
        question: "What instrument does Phoebe play?",
        "option": [
            "Guitar",
            "Violin",
            "Piano",
            "Ukulele"],
        correct: "Guitar"
    },
    {
        number: 8,
        question: "Where are Ross, Rachel, and Monica from?",
        "option": [
            "Connecticut",
            "Long Island",
            "New Jersey",
            "Westchester"],
        correct: "Long Island"
    },
    {
        number: 9,
        question: "What is the name of the coffee house the Friends hangout at?",
        "option": [
            "Central Perk",
            "Starbucks",
            "Central Coffee",
            "NYC Perks"],
        correct: "Central Perk"
    },
    {
        number: 10,
        question: "Where do the Friends all live?",
        "option": [
            "Chicago",
            "Los Angeles",
            "New York City",
            "Houston"],
        correct: "New York City"
    },
    {
        number: 11,
        question: "Who is the paleontologist?",
        "option": [
            "Joey",
            "Ross",
            "Monica",
            "Chandler"],
        correct: "Ross"
    },
    {
        number: 12,
        question: "Which Friend dates Janice first?",
        "option": [
            "Joey",
            "Ross",
            "Chandler",
            "Gunther"],
        correct: "Chandler"
    },
    {
        number: 13,
        question: "What does Monica do for work?",
        "option": [
            "She's a waitress",
            "She's a massesuse",
            "She's a doctor",
            "She's a chef"],
        correct: "She's a chef"
    },
    {
        number: 14,
        question: "What does Joey do for work?",
        "option": [
            "Singer",
            "Model",
            "Actor",
            "Nothing"],
        correct: "Actor"
    },
    {
        number: 15,
        question: "What show do Joey and Chandler love to watch?",
        "option": [
            "Jeopardy",
            "Baywatch",
            "Wheel of Fortune",
            "Days of Our Lives"],
        correct: "Baywatch"
    },
    {
        number: 16,
        question: "Which pets do Joey and Chandler have?",
        "option": [
            "Dogs",
            "A chick and a duck",
            "Cats",
            "Rat babies"],
        correct: "A chick and a duck"
    },
    {
        number: 17,
        question: "Which pets do Joey and Chandler have?",
        "option": [
            "Dogs",
            "A chick and a duck",
            "Cats",
            "Rat babies"],
        correct: "A chick and a duck"
    },
    {
        number: 18,
        question: "What is the neighbor's name that lives below Rachel and Monica?",
        "option": [
            "Mr. Heckles",
            "Mr. Treiger",
            "Gunther",
            "Mr. Sheck"],
        correct: "Mr. Heckles"
    },
    {
        number: 19,
        question: "What is Ross' monkey's name?",
        "option": [
            "Paolo",
            "Marcus",
            "Sir",
            "Marcel"],
        correct: "Marcel"
    },
    {
        number: 20,
        question: "What does Ross buy for Rachel's birthday?",
        "option": [
            "A necklace",
            "A brooch",
            "Flowers",
            "A sweater"],
        correct: "A brooch"
    },
];